<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Panoramic Screenshot \"Resurrection\"</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="compose">Compose</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="progress_diff">Image %d and %d of %d</string>
    <string name="composing">Composing&#8230;</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="saved_to">Picture saved to %s</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="sensitivity_text">Sensitivity: %.2f</string>
    <string name="skip_text">Skip Ratio: %.2f</string>
    <string name="sample_ratio_text">Subsample Ratio: %.0f</string>
    <string name="options_note">Note: options below do not affect the resolution and dimension of the final product.</string>
    <string name="not_enough_pictures">Please choose 2 or more pictures first.</string>
    <string name="dimension_mismatch">Picture dimension mismatch.</string>
    <string name="no_common_part">Cannot find common parts between pictures. Please check and ensure added pictures do share common regions and are in the correct order. If they do, please try decreasing sensitivity in options.</string>
    <string name="loading_pictures">Loading pictures&#8230;</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="options_help_txt">
        Panoramic Screenshot composes pictures by first scanning them in pairs and compare
        which parts are common among each pair.
        Below are parameters available for tweaking the scan-and-compare process.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>

        &lt;b>Sensitivity&lt;/b>: Controls how much (in percentage) of two lines should be the same in order to consider them identical.
        This is useful if the screenshots contain minor obstructions, e.g. scroll bars. If you see too much artifact
        in the result, try increasing this; if the result is totally incorrect, try decreasing this.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>

        &lt;b>Skip Ratio&lt;/b>: When comparing each pair, how much of the first picture (from the top) and the second picture (from the bottom)
        should the algorithm ignore. This can reduce the scanning time dramatically because the overlapping area between each pair
        should only appear at the bottom of the first and at the top of the second.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>

        &lt;b>Subsample Ratio&lt;/b>: When comparing, scale each image down by this amount (e.g. 4 times by default) first. This also reduces
        scanning time and will not affect the result if not too large. This will not affect the final resolution. Image will still
        be concatenated in their original size.
    </string>
</resources>
